Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
Center for Digital Research in the Humanities University of Nebraska–Lincoln
- Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Daniel Hurt; 1829,; assault and battery on Negro Harry Wallace (Box 420, Folder 59)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. V. Negress Leah Ann Deane; 1829,; stealing "one piece of Calico" worth $8.00 (Box 420, Folder 63)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Richard; 1829,; stealing $29 in banknotes (Box 420, Folder 87)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Thomas Brown; 1829,; assault and battery (Box 420, Folder 91)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Richard James; 1829,; assault and battery (Box 420, Folder 121)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Ben Wheeler; 1829,; stealing four pieces of silver money worth $1.00 (Box 420, Folder 132)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro Lawson Goings; 1829,; assault and battery on "Negro Miller" (Box 420, Folder 139)
  - May, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Negro William; 1829,; stealing $40 in banknotes (Box 420, Folder 148)
  - May, Civil Trials, 15-225, Samuel I. Potts et al. v. John Holtzman; 1829,; includes a newspaper advertisement for the auction of "one NEGRO BOY named LEWIS, about fourteen years of age" (Box 421, Folder 188)
  - May, Civil Trials, 15-225, Christopher Harris v. Robert Rowley; 1829,; petition for freedom (Box 421, Folder 234)
  - May, Civil Trials, 227-337, 1829 (Box 422)
  - May, Civil Trials, 338-444, 1829 (Box 423)
  - May, Judicials, 1-182, 1829 (Box 424)
  - Judicials, 184-221, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1829 (Box 425)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, H.T. Weightman v. H.B. Davis; 1829, December; "one negro woman...about 40 years old" $ 80.00 (Box 426, Folder 31)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, John Kurtz v. Union Bank of Georgetown; 1829, December; "one negro man or boy called Richard Clarke about five feet five inches high" $275.00 (Box 426, Folder 35)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, Rebecca Taylor v. J.P. Ball; 1829, December; "one negro man...about 40 years of age" $200.00 (Box 426, Folder 46)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, Urania Chappell v. E.H. Healy; 1829, December; "one negro man...aged about 21 years" $400.00 (Box 426, Folder 157)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, Maria White v. Joseph M. White; 1829, December; petition for freedom (Box 426, Folder 166)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-178, E.N. Childs v. George Milburn; 1829, December; "one negro girl...aged about 10 years" $150.00 (Box 426, Folder 171)
  - Civil Appearances, 180-495, Benjamin Burns v. John E. Berry; 1829, December; bill of sale for "my negro woman, named Charlott, and her child" appraised at $300.00, sold for $260.00 (Box 427, Folder 227 1/2)
  - Civil Appearances, 180-495, Seraphim Masi v. John E. Berry; 1829, December; "one negro boy../aged about 19 years" $300.00 (Box 427, Folder 306)
  - Civil Appearances, 180-495, Richard H. Williams v. Joseph M. White; 1829, December; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians does not list Joseph M. White as the defendant (Box 427, Folder 468)
  - Civil Trials, 1-163, 1829, December (Box 428)
  - Civil Trials, 165-266, Leonard Harbaugh v. John Waters; 1829, December; "one negro boy...aged about 14 years" $180.00 (Box 429, Folder 249)
  - Civil Trials, 268-358, 1829, December (Box 430)
  - Civil Trials 360-389, Appeals, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, James Galt V. Henry G. Wilson; 1829, December; "100 DOLLARS REWARD—Runaway from the Subscriber living in Georgetown, D.C., Sunday morning, August 3d, two likely young negro men, both bright mulattoes." (Box 431, Folder 363)
  - Imparlances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1829, December (Box 432)
  - Judicials, 1-117, Daniel D. Arden v. Lemuel Sawyer; 1829, December; "one negro woman...aged about 22 years" $100.00 (Box 433, Folder 34)
  - Judicials, 1-117, Bank of the Metropolis v. Samuel Burch; 1829, December; "one negro boy...aged 13 years" $300.00 (Box 433, Folder 55)
  - Judicials, 1-117, G. Adrone v. N.L. Queen & W.H. Gunnell; 1829, December; "negro Dennis aged about 22 years" $300.00 Family of James Price ("aged about 40"); wife, 35, three daughters, 12, 10 and 7, three sons, 11, 9 and infant appraised at $600.00 (Box 433, Folder 56)
  - Judicials, 1-117, U.S. V. Edgar Cupid; 1829, December; $1.00 fine (Box 433, Folder 89)
  - Judicials, 118-372, U.S. v. William Chubb; 1829, December; $100 fine, each case (in none of these cases is the defendant’s race mentioned, either in the papers or in the docket book) (Box 434, Folder 119, 120)
  - Judicials, 118-372, Walter Clarke v. Samuel Burch et al.; 1829, December; "one negro boy...aged about 20 years" $400.00 (Box 434, Folder 309)
  - Judicials, 118-372, John F. Webb v. Robert Keyworth; 1829, December; "one negro boy...aged about 15 years" $200.00 (Box 434)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-179, Valentine Carter V. John H. Beall; 1830,; "one negro boy named George calls himself George Sprigg aged about 17 years" $300.00 (Box 435, Folder 33, 34)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-179, W.G.W, White v. John H. Beall; 1830,; George Sprigg, appraised at $340.00 (Box 435, Folder 46)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-179, Nancy Cox v. James Cox; 1830,; petition for freedom (Box 435, Folder 52)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-179, Sylvia Lee v. Elizabeth Smallwood; 1830,; petition for freedom (Box 435, Folder 72)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 188-449, Benjamin L. Gantt v. Abraham Clarke; 1830,; "one negro boy...about 12 years of age" $160.00 (Box 436, Folder 392)
  - May, Civil Trials, 2-179, James Smith v. Walter P. Newton; 1830,; petition for freedom (Box 437, Folder 57)
  - May, Civil Trials, 2-179, Negro Charlotte and children v. Henry Clay; 1830,; petition for freedom (Box 437, Folder 121)
  - May, Civil Trials, 181-282, 1830 (Box 438)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, William Green v. Elisha Jewell; 1830,; petition for freedom (Box 439, Folder 322)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Ennis Scott; 1830,; assault (Box 439, Folder 5)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Robert Johnson; 1830,; drew a knife on a constable (Box 439, Folder 21)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William Butler; 1830,; assault on John Deane (Box 439, Folder 22)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William Butler; 1830,; assault on James A. Deane (Box 439, Folder 23)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Samuel Butler; 1830,; assault (Box 439, Folder 26)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Arnold Green; 1830,; assault (Box 439, Folder 33)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Benjamin Tate; 1830,; stole 1/2 bbl herring worth $2; ten mackerel worth 50 cents (Box 439, Folder 99)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Nelson Sims; 1830,; stole one axe worth $1.50 (Box 439, Folder 118)
  - May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. James Clements; 1830,; stole one comb worth $600 (Box 439, Folder 127)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Harriet Anderson v. Corporation of Washington; 1830,; case of breaking curfew "a free negro—was found in one of the streets of the City of Washington...at a later hour than half after 10 o’clock" (Box 440, Folder 23)
  - May, Judicials, 1-214, Margaret Baltzer V. William Y. Wetzel; 1830,; "maintenance of Negro Moses,...Negress Julia Ann,...Sarah,...Susan & Jacob in Jail" (one week) $10.88 (Box 441, Folder 163)
  - May, Judicials, 1-214, C & O Canal Co. v. James Kennedy; 1830,; "one black boy...aged about 16 years" $300.00 (Box 441)
  - May, Judicials, 216-321, Titlings for Executions & Writs, John Kidglie v. George A. Smoot; 1830,; "one negro girl...aged about 13 years" $200.00 (Box 442, Folder 247)
  - May, Judicials, 216-321, Titlings for Executions & Writs, Benjamin Burns v. Robert Keyworth; 1830,; "one negro boy...aged about 16 years" $325.00 (Box 442, Folder 256)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-196, Susan Wilson v. William Addison; 1830, December; petition for freedom (Box 443, Folder 131)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-196, Sylvia Lee v. Elizabeth Smallwood; 1830, December; petition for freedom (Box 443, Folder 177)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-196, Negro Gerrard v. Zachariah Cox; 1830, December; petition for freedom (Box 443, Folder 180)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-196, Ann Williams and children v. George Miller; 1830, December; petition for freedom (Box 443, Folder 181)
  - Civil Appearances, 198-566, William Hurley v. J.B. Lock & J.W. Brick; 1830, December; negro woman name Hanah, aged about 45 years $100.00 (Box 444, Folder 310)
  - Civil Appearances, 198-566, Negro Mary and child v. Lewin Talburt; 1830, December; petition for freedom (Box 444, Folder 451)
  - Civil Appearances, 569-612, Civil Trials, 2-138, Walter B. Beale v. Lambert S. Beck; 1830, December; Beck "took...one negro slave named William ...and unjustly detained him against sureties & pledges...whereby [Beale] saith that he is injured & hath damage to the value of a thousand dollars..." (Box 445, Folder 92)
  - Civil Trials, 141-259, Jesse A. Dollerhide v. George Milburn; 1830, December; "one negro or rnulatto girl...about fifteen years of age" $206.25 (Box 446, Folder 95)
  - Civil Trials, 260-331, Criminal Appearances, 1-36, U.S. v. Alexander Young; 1830, December; assault & battery on constable (Box 447, Folder 24)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. John Sanders; 1830, December; assault & battery (Box 448, Folder 72)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. James Colbert; 1830, December; stole a spade worth $1.00 and a clothesline worth 50 cents (Box 448, Folder 127)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Ann Talbutt; 1830, December; stole three pairs of shoes worth $4.00 (Box 448, Folder 129)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Ann Talbutt; 1830, December; stole two quilts worth $1.50 and one chest worth $3.50 (Box 448, Folder 132)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Nancy Ashton; 1830, December; stole one cloak worth $1.00 (Box 448, Folder 148)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U .S. v. Caroline Calvert; 1830, December; cut Nancy Ashton with an axe (Box 448, Folder 156)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Thomas Rollins; 1830, December; stole one pair of shoes worth $1.12 (Box 448, Folder 159)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. William Chubb; 1830, December; stole eight dozen herrings worth 80 cents (Box 448, Folder 161)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, US. v. Jim Davis; 1830, December; stole $50 in banknotes and $3 in silver money (Box 448, Folder 172)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. John Barnes; 1830, December; stole one cheese worth $1.00 (Box 448, Folder 175)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Horace Gales; 1830, December; same thet as Jim Davis, #172 (Box 448, Folder 176)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Thomas Johnson; 1830, December; stole one blanket worth $1.25 (Box 448, Folder 177)
  - Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, US. v. Rezin Barker; 1830, December; stole one overcoat worth $15; 1 pr gloves worth 50 cents (Box 448, Folder 187)
  - Appeals, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1830, December; In Miscellaneous file, testimony of Zedekiah Kidwell "relative to the price of a Colored Boy said to be a slave" (Box 449, Folder rough bundle)
  - Imparlances, Judicials, 1-181, 1830, December (Box 450)
  - Judicials, 182-385, 1830, December (Box 451)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 1-188, Adam Wigle v. Thomas Grimes; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 452, Folder 36)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 1-188, Sylvia Lee v. Elizabeth Smallwood; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 452, Folder 59)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 1-188, Negro Gerrard v. Zachariah Cox; 1831,; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians lists the petitioner as Leonard (Box 452, Folder 62)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 197-378, Negro Kitty v. Samuel McPherson; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 453, Folder 371)
  - May, Civil Trials, 2-147, Thomas Butler et al. v. Gabriel Duvall; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 454, Folder 80)
  - May, Civil Trials, 2-147, William Thornton v. George M. Graham; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 454, Folder 82)
  - May, Civil Trials, 2-147, George W. Wilson v. John E. Berry; 1831,; "One negro boy named Spencer Allen aged about 19 years" $400.00 (Box 454, Folder 121)
  - May, Civil Trials, 149-205, 1831 (Box 455)
  - May, Civil Trials, 209-328, Arnold T. Windsor v. Marshal S. Wines; 1831,; a bill totaling $197.45 includes, among other charges, the labor of slaves Samuel, Joshua and Seth, who hired out for $10 a month for 44 days (Box 456, Folder 305)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, U.S. V. Horace Gales; 1831,; stole $50 in notes and $3 in silver money (Box 457, Folder 22)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1831; Habeas Corpus petition of Garrison Hanson, "a Freeman,...born of free Parents..." (Box 457, Folder rough bundle)
  - May, Imparlances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, Negro Mary v. Lewin Talburt; 1831,; petition for freedom (Box 458, Folder 427)
  - May, Judicials, 1-171, John J. Palmer v. Peter Force; 1831,; "One negro man...aged about 21 years" $350.00 (Box 459, Folder 19)
  - May, Judicials, 1-171, Erasmus J. Middleton v. Henry S. Wood; 1831,; sale ($220) and maintenance (thirteen days @34 cents=$4.42) of Negro Adeline (Box 459, Folder 24)
  - May, Judicials, 1-171, John B. Benson v. Thomas N. Miller; 1831,; sale of 5 men (ages 20-40), mother (30) and child (10), for $1450.00 (Box 459, Folder 61)
  - May, Judicials, 173-285, 1831 (Box 460)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Croxton Monday v. Henry T. Garnett; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 461, Folder 13)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Susan Wilson v. William Addison; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 461, Folder 80)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Sylvia Lee V. Elizabeth Smallwood; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 461, Folder 93)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Negro Gerrard v. Zachariah Cox; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 461, Folder 96)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Ann Williams and children v. George Miller; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 461, Folder 97)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-191, Isaac Bartlett v. Gerrard T. Greenﬁeld; 1831, December; "one mulatto girl" ("about 16") $200.00 "one yellow negro woman...aged about 35 years and her mulatto child named Daniel Alexander" (3 years 9 months) $200.00 (Box 461, Folder 187)
  - Civil Appearances, 198-574, Samuel Smith v. Jesse Conn; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 462, Folder 239)
  - Civil Trials, 2-151, John Queen v. Tench Ringgold; 1831, December; "1 negro woman...aged about 25 years" $200.00 (Box 463, Folder 25)
  - Civil Trials, 156-315, 1831, December (Box 464)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, Emanuel Gilbert v. Horatio M. Ward; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 465, Folder 329)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, Nelly Lemon and children v. John H. Bayne; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 465, Folder 385)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, Negro Sam v. Lewis Childs et al.; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 465, Folder 391)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, Negro Ned v. Lewis Childs et al.; 1831, December; petition for freedom (Box 465, Folder 392)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William Patterson; 1831, December; assault & battery on Kitty Patterson includes letter from Robert J. And William G. Patterson to "Ornebell Mr Francis S Key," describing how the woman "sezed" Patterson "by his privets and sade you son of Bitch...and he sade in sepplication seven ore 8 times to let him Go...at lenth he Strouck her in self Defence...next morning his piivets war as Blake as my hat and bleding all so by the Polling of them..." (Box 465, Folder 41)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Robert Johnson; 1831, December; stealing a pair of shoes worth $200 (Box 465, Folder 57)
  - Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Hiram J. Emerson; 1831, December; contempt, assaulted Samuel A. Childs in the courthouse, in the course of a "conversation...upon the subject of a suit instituted in this Court by sundry slaves against [Emerson] and others for the recovery of their freedom..." "I gave [Childs] the lie," Emerson said, and then got violent. This case probably tells more about slaveholders than about slaves.... (Box 465, Folder 74, 76)
  - Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, Cary Seldon V. Alexander Keech; 1831, December; "I hereby agree to pay to Mr Alexr Keetch...for the hire of his negroe man John Parsons for one year...at the rate of Thirty dollars..." (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - Imparlances, 1831, December (Box 467)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-338, Nelly Lemon and children v. John H. Bayne; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 468, Folder 60)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-338, Negro Ann Williams and children v. G. Miller; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 468, Folder 89)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-338, Negro Ned Douglass v. Richard B. Mason; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 468, Folder 90)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 5-338, H. Smith V. J. & E. Peter; 1832,; "one negro man...aged about 45 years" $200.00 (Box 468, Folder 337)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 341-541, Civil Trials, 12-102, Joel T. Gustine v. Tench Ringgold; 1832,; six boys and girls, aged 8-16, appraised from $150 to $250, and one woman, aged 60, appraised at $25.00 (Box 469, Folder 84)
  - May, Civil Trial, 106-252, Samuel Heinecke V. Elizabeth Beall; 1832,; "one negro girl...aged about 21 years" $300.00 (Box 470, Folder 119)
  - May, Civil Trial, 106-252, Samuel Burch V. Tench Ringgold; 1832,; "one negro man...aged about 40 years" $175.00 (Box 470, Folder 126)
  - May, Civil Trials, 255-375, Henry Edmonson v. Joseph Neale; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 471, Folder 371)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. V. Benjamin Lundy; 1832,; "an agent for procuring subscriptions and for circulating among free negroes and slaves...a seditious & mischievous news paper,...‘The Liberator’...." (Box 472, Folder 11)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. William Lloyd Garrison, Isaac Knapp; 1832,; "editors and publishers of a scandalous & mischievous news paper titled ‘The Liberator’...for the purpose of inﬂaming & exciting the free negroes & slaves to insurrection..." (Box 472, Folder 12, 13)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Richard Rounds; 1832,; stealing carpenter’s tools worth $550 (Box 472, Folder 15)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Negro Nelson Harper; 1832,; murder of Negro William Davis (Box 472, Folder 31)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Negro Rezin Barber; 1832,; stealing bed, bedclothes worth $12.50 (Box 472, Folder 61)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Washington Williams; 1832,; same oﬁense (Box 472, Folder 62)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Williams (Washington Williams’s mother); 1832,; same offense (Box 472, Folder 63)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, U.S. v. Henry Barker; 1832,; stealing banknotes and a check worth $154.00 (Box 472, Folder 65)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1832; Habeas corpus petition of Negroes Harriet and Kitty (daughter of Nelly Lemon—see December term 1831, Civil Trials 385) (Box 472, Folder 96)
  - May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1832; Case of Alfred and Charles Hines, two black housebreakers in Alexandria County (only Alexandria County case l’ve come across so far; must be an oversight) (Box 472, Folder rough bundle)
  - May, Imparlances, L. Thompson v. J.B. Locke & J.W. Beck; 1832,; "negro woman...about 27 years" $200.00 (Box 473, Folder 38)
  - May, Imparlances, Ann Key v. Robert Robertson; 1832,; "negro woman" (no age), ﬁve year-old daughter and two month-old son $400.00 (Box 473, Folder 192)
  - May, Judicials, 1832 (Box 474)
  - November, Civil Appearances, 7-391, Sylvia Lee v. Elizabeth Smallwood; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 475, Folder 122)
  - November, Civil Appearances, 7-391, Negro Gerrard v. Zachariah Cox; 1832,; petition for freedom (Box 475, Folder 123)
  - November, Civil Appearances, 7-391, George B. Magruder v. Henry Roberts; 1832,; "negro woman...about 30 years" $200.00 (Box 475, Folder 224)
  - November, Civil Appearances, 399-686, Civil Trials, 5-147, 1832 (Box 476)
  - November, Civil Trials, 150-152, Anthony Holmead v. Oliver Simpson; 1832,; "negro boy...about ten years" $200.00 (Box 477, Folder 197)
  - November, Civil Trials, 262-408, John B. Holmead v. Michael Gannon; 1832,; "negro man...about 40 years" $300.00 (Box 478, Folder 401)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Horatio M. Ward v. James Williams; 1832,; "to maintenance of Emanuel Gilbert in jail as your slave" 120 days @ 34 cents; 1 pr pantaloons, $2.75; 1 shirt, 75 cents $47.52 (Box 479, Folder Appeals 4)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
  - November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)